You'd leave if I were even
a minute late for tutoring.
Why did you wait?
Well, it's just...
Have you grown attached?
What?
I think you have
grown fond of me?
You text me
as soon as you wake up.
We see each other
every day in class.
We text each other
until we fall asleep.
Come on, spill it.
Have you grown fond of me?
You don't seem sorry at all.
Sorry for the 51st time.
In that spirit, I'll
give you a special lesson.
Keep your elbow
perpendicular to the floor.
Always keep your
eyes on the hoop.
Keep your wrist relaxed.
And then
snap it at the end.
Alright, now shoot.
It's in.
You're pretty good
Han Se-woon.
Great.
Shall we get started for real?
Three...
Two!
When I say one, you go.